Thank you, Kadir.
Excellent.
Please tell your wife
she makes it even better
than they did in Constantinople.
I think you mean Istanbul, ma'am.
Constantinople, this is its ancient name.
Of course.
The Black Sky.
We have it.
How long
have you waited for this?
Too long.
This will use
the last of our resources.
Are you sure it is a risk worth taking?
I have never been more sure of anything.
I know you're afraid, but that will pass.
So will the pain.
It's all right.
Stand down.
This is your home now.
We are your family.
I have waited so long to meet you.
Easy.
Easy, my child. Easy.
Go ahead.
You'll need your strength.
Language will come back to you.
So will your instincts.
But everything else...
I'm afraid it wasn't worth keeping anyway.
You...
My name is Alexandra.
You were born.
You lived and died.
And what you saw on the other side...
the darkness, the absence of everything...
it's horrifying, isn't it?
I have seen it, too.
More than once.
And all I want in this life
is never to see it again.
But now that we've been
brought together...
that's not something
we need to worry about.
Who?
My child...
you... are everything.
You are everything.
It doesn't matter what you choose.
You are the Black Sky.
In the end, you are the weapon.
Wakizashi.
Good choice.
They won't know what's coming
till it's too late.
She's ready.
Bring it to her.
You asked me a question.
This is the answer.
This is who you are.
She's ready for you.
The war that you've been fighting
your entire life, Stick, it's over.
Long as Iron Fist lives, nothing's over.
Where is he?
Damned if I know.
We're not doing
the torture song and dance.
Not anymore.
Shame.
I grew to like that part.
Danny Rand has been running around
off the grid for months.
He thinks he's a one-man army.
He's a real handful.
I've seen better.
Still, you'll spend the rest of your days
looking over your shoulder.
And from what I hear...
those days are numbered.
Now...
- that's the Alexandra I know.
- Pay attention.
You make a new friend?
No, Stick.
I took one of yours.
- Elektra.
- The vessel you knew is gone.
Only the Black Sky lives.
Listen to me, kid.
She's full of shit.
- We gotta get you out...
- Where is the Iron Fist?
I'll die before I let him join your army.
You think I want him to fight for me?
He's a weapon. You're a monster.
What else?
After a lifetime of serving K'un-Lun...
you don't even know what he is.
No.
But I know what I am.
You asked for it... Elektra.
You'll die here tonight, old man.
- Finally.
- Don't you bet on it.
Son of a bitch.
- Are you a public defender?
- Uh, no.
- Then what are you doing here?
- A friend referred me. He works for...
- Let me guess, Jeri Hogarth.
- Right.
I didn't know she did diversity hires.
Uh, I'm independent.
I don't work for her firm.
- Well, I'm not paying you.
- You don't have to.
- Oh, 'cause she'll foot the bill?
- Yeah.
And I'm a Catholic.
I have a soft spot for hopeless causes.
- That was a bad joke. Sorry.
- Barely.
Uh, Ms. Jones, may I ask
how long you've been a PI?
No.
Are you always this rude
to people trying to help you?
You know what?
I'm gonna find my own lawyer, thanks.
Okay. Uh, well, in reality,
you don't need one.
After talking
to the lead detective outside,
it appears that despite the mess
you got yourself into,
the NYPD doesn't actually have anything
to hold you on, so...
- So I can walk?
- Mm-hmm.
Though your apartment and office are
still considered an active crime scene.
You'll need to make yourself available
for follow-up questions,
- so in the meantime...
- Don't leave town.
Yeah, I know the drill.
Ms. Jones, can... May... Uh...
Look, there's no easy way to say this.
I read your file. I know who you are.
What you can do.
I know what happened
with Kilgrave, so if...
- This has nothing to do with that.
- Okay, great. Then...
Look, I'm... I'm just saying, legally,
if there's anything,
this will stay between us if...
this was... There's anything not, uh,
ordinary about this case.
What part of "I know the drill"
did you not understand?
Nothing happened.
I'm good.
Great. Then I guess you're free to go.
Malcolm? Yeah, I just gave my statement.
Are you okay?
What exactly did you tell them?
Hey.
- What happened?
- Hey.
The kids are being recruited by some guy
known on the streets as White Hat.
I don't know what he's up to,
but they're doing
some kind of clean-up work.
- Cleaning up what?
- I didn't get a look, but...
What's wrong?
That kid, Cole...
cops just picked him up.
- He's probably in jail by now.
- Hmm.
- I left him behind, Claire.
- It's okay.
No, it's not.
You're better off not in prison.
I like you here.
What happened?
I got clocked.
- By White Hat?
- No. I don't know who he was.
But when he hit me,
it felt like a sledgehammer.
He had this... this hand.
I think it glowed.
Glowed how?
I don't know. Just some skinny white kid.
He had this fist and...
- Who you calling?
- There's someone that you need to meet.
- He punched me.
- You punched first.
Seriously?
- How come he can't be hurt?
- What's the deal with that fist?
- I earned it.
- You what?
He earned it.
There's this mystical place
called K'un-Lun, and it's...
I can answer myself.
- There's a mystical place called K'un-Lun.
- Oh, this is a joke. Come on.
My parents died in a plane crash.
I was adopted by a group of monks.
There, I learned how to summon my chi.
I'm the Immortal Iron Fist.
Is this why you went to China?
Whatever it is that you saw last night,
this White Hat guy...
could be connected to the people
Danny and Colleen have been fighting.
The same people who attacked the hospital
that Claire was working at.
You're saying you know
who this White Hat guy is?
No. But I think he's with the Hand.
It's a criminal organization.
No telling how old they are.
Nor how much influence
they have. They are everywhere.
In everything.
All of their power stems
from their ability to bring back the dead.
Okay, I don't know
how much of this I can take.
- This sounds insane.
- And so does being bulletproof.
The two of you trust me,
so please listen when I say...
you're on the same side.
Now, we're gonna leave you two alone,
and you're gonna talk.
Talk.
Couple months ago,
we were planning a vacation.
He wanted to get away.
Doesn't make sense.
I came to you...
for answers. And now...
Well, the NYPD is on the case, but...
...between us,
I would like to keep investigating.
- You mean without the police?
- Yeah.
- I don't know how much I can afford.
- Don't worry about that right now.
Okay. Okay.
Now, is there anything
you haven't told me?
Drugs? You know, gambling,
weird fetish shit? Was there any world
- that he was a part of?
- No. No.
Why? What did you see?
I think someone was targeting him.
What do you mean?
I'm not sure.
None of this sounds like John.
He wasn't this kind of person.
And there's nothing I'm not telling you.
There's nothing I don't know.
He loved two things.
He loved us and his job.
And that's it. That was his whole life.
I'll be right back.
- Hi, sweetie. How are you?
- Hi, Mom. I'm okay.
I'm sure we'll find out soon.
Why don't we lay you down,
and you can let me fix you supper.
Hey.
I'm sorry about what happened.
Um... tell your mom I let myself out.
Hello?
Hi, I'm returning
a call from Ms. Anna Asher.
- What?
- This is Duncan and Dotter Design.
Oh, right, this is her. Sorry.
- Um, can you come in this afternoon?
- Sure.
211 10th Avenue, suite 305.
- 305. Got it.
- Thank you, Ms. Asher.
You can fight.
You can take a punch.
Claire said they did experiments on you.
Long story.
What kind?
Was it voluntary?
They made me this way.
That's all you need to know.
What did you mean, "chi"?
It's a... It's an energy force.
- Okay.
- We all have it.
Not like that.
I trained for years.
There was a test.
There was a dragon.
No, there wasn't.
It's going better
than I thought it would.
I know how it sounds,
but it's true.
You gotta admit,
that dragon shit, from the outside...
- does sound pretty crazy.
- Mm-hmm.
You really think
they can help each other out?
I don't know.
Once they're done
with the pissing contest...
...who knows?
Claire says you're a good guy.
I'm trying.
She says you've done a lot for Harlem.
Yeah, I just... just wanna help.
Me, too.
That's what led me to that warehouse.
You call that helping? You were gonna
beat that kid within an inch of his life.
Come on.
I wasn't gonna kill him.
It sure looked like it.
The Hand is dangerous.
They murdered my parents.
Invaded the city I was sworn to protect.
That kid's got nothing
to do with all that.
Of course he does. He works for them.
- He needed a job.
- That's not an excuse.
You never fought someone
to protect someone else?
- Of course I have.
- Okay, so what's the difference?
The difference is I live on their block.
The difference is
I'm not some billionaire white boy
who takes justice into his own hands
and slams a black kid against the wall
because of his personal vendetta.
Claire told me about you
on the way over here.
Not all the mystical parts,
but everything else.
The money?
That doesn't define me.
Maybe not, but that kid is sitting
in a jail cell tonight and you're not.
- Neither are you.
- Not this time.
But I've seen my share of injustice.
The guy in the white hat,
he's just the beginning.
You're not thinking
about the bigger picture.
about anything but yourself.
Hey! You know nothing about me.
I know enough.
And I know privilege when I see it.
You may think you earned your strength,
but you had power the day you were born.
Before the dragons. Before the chi.
You have the ability to change the world
without getting anybody hurt.
These people won't be stopped that way.
You're taking the war
to the ones at the bottom, is that it?
If I were in your shoes, I'd think twice
about using that thing on people
who are trying to feed their families.
This isn't gonna work out, it's obvious.
Good luck, man.
I'm sorry.
I know you're having a rough time in here.
Yeah.
Misty says you'll be arraigned
within 24 hours...
but we can figure this out.
Has anyone approached you
about making a deal?
I know a lawyer.
There ain't no deal.
There were dead bodies in there.
Looks like you were doing grunt work.
Like you were helping to clean up.
- Look, it doesn't matter.
- Of course it does.
You don't take the blame
for something that's not yours.
- Whoever hired you...
- Man, would you wake up?
They're watching everything.
They got eyes and ears all over.
And the longer you talk to me,
the worse it looks.
For the both of us.
- Who's the guy in the white hat?
- Man, would you stay away?
He is next-level dangerous.
So am I.
Is this the Hand?
You wanna help me?
My mom, she lives at 555 Edgecombe.
Take her some lotto tickets.
Tell her they're from me.
Cole, just tell me what you know.
Scratch-off. Those are her favorite,
all right? Just do it.
Tell her that they're from me.
Tell her that I'm thinking about her.
- You can trust me.
- I do.
Tell her I'm sorry.
Looks like that big guy
made quite an impression, huh?
I am glad that you two
didn't end up in a fist fight.
'Cause I'm not sure
that this place would survive it.
What if he's right?
About what?
The Fist is one way to win this war,
but I do have others.
Yeah... and you've tried 'em.
They're the Hand, you can't just buy 'em.
I'm not talking about money.
I have connections, access.
He doesn't understand
what we're really up against.
He doesn't get how dangerous they are.
I know, but...
why am I fighting street-level operatives
when I have the power
to go right to the top?
Because, Danny, you...
You're not a businessman.
I know.
But my father was.
I know, but you are a fighter.
A warrior.
That's what you know.
That's... that's what's in your heart.
And a good warrior uses
every tool at his disposal.
I own 51% of a major corporation.
I've got to try this another way.
Hello? This is Danny Rand.
Welcome back, Mr. Rand.
Mr. Meachum mentioned you had
business to take care of abroad.
Uh, yeah. That's what brings me here.
Where is Ward?
On a business trip himself.
Perhaps we could schedule
something for next month?
I, uh, don't have time for that.
Well, unfortunately,
that's the earliest he'll be available.
There was an organization
that did business with us last year.
- We did lots of business.
- Yeah, they call themselves the Hand.
- You need help spelling that?
- Look, whatever you heard, it's true.
I know you're scared,
but we can't leave until you help us.
- Help you how?
- We tailed 'em.
We tracked 'em to São Paulo.
Berlin. Moscow.
They set up shell companies, worldwide.
We think they're doing
something here in New York.
We need you to help us find it.
- São Paulo, Berlin and Moscow?
- Uh-huh.
Anywhere else?
- Uh, Paris, Miami...
- Phnom Penh, Cambodia.
I'm cross-referencing short-term holdings
through those cities.
Two hundred exist in the overlap.
Three of them shut down last year.
What does that mean?
Not much, except that they
were shut down on the same day.
Before they closed, they all made deposits
into one place here in New York.
I just need a name.
Um... Midland Circle Financial.
I remember that name.
Ward gave us a list of places
to cease doing business with.
It must be the Hand.
I'll get you the address
from the directory.
Thank you.
We hit tonight. After hours.
No.
There's another way to attack.
And I gotta do this alone.
- Gorgeous, isn't it?
- Mmm.
Like all of our projects,
it was built with sustainability in mind.
- Yeah, I am super into that.
- I'm glad, Ms. Asher.
Now, why don't you tell me
what you envisioned for your company's...
- Communal workspace.
- Ah.
Um, I mean, we're gonna need a juice bar.
- Of course.
- Uh, standing desks.
You know those bouncy balls that people
sit on that some people find annoying?
I think it should be modern
and high-tech, but also so simple.
A pragmatic utopia.
Yes. Oh, my God. Can I quote that?
Don't answer. I'm gonna quote that.
Here is a property
I worked on last year in Midtown.
Huh.
Is there anything more recent?
- I'm sorry?
- Anything from this year?
- Not that I've done.
- Mmm.
How about any other architect
in your firm?
Just because it's really important
for our brand
that we're not only on the cutting edge,
but we are the cutting edge.
Yes, but...
can you keep a secret?
I am the face of discretion.
I can show you our most recent work.
A building in Hell's Kitchen,
designed by my colleague John Raymond.
- Wow.
- Midland Circle.
And is that architect on the premises?
I would love to speak with him.
No, he's... not. Not at the moment.
And who were the clients?
That's privileged information.
I'm sure you understand.
Uh, but I do have another structure
that you might be interested in.
One that we unveiled in Soho last winter.
- If you just give me a minute?
- Great.
Hi.
We met the other night.
Oh, we didn't meet, son.
God himself sent you.
You don't have to hide anything from me.
I know where Cole is.
He's following in his brother's footsteps.
You know what kind of trouble
they were into?
No.
But I hear there are bodies.
Don't sound like my son,
but I've been wrong before.
I can't help but feel some shame,
to be honest.
But ain't nothing I can do now.
Except to pray.
I believe in the power of prayer.
My father made sure of it.
But it might not be too late.
Cole was working for some bad people.
I'm going to stop 'em.
May the Lord bless and keep you
for doing his work.
- Only doing what's needed.
- Oh.
You know, you're the opposite from my son.
He can't admit
when he's done something wrong.
You can't admit
when you done something right.
Uh, Cole wanted me to bring these to you.
They're lotto tickets.
He said he wanted you to know
he was thinking about you.
There is goodness in that boy.
You know, he'd been bringin' me these
since he was eight years old?
At first, I didn't know
how he was paying for them.
And then I realized
he was using his lunch money.
He said it was worth it...
to keep the dream alive.
How 'bout some cookies? Chocolate chip.
Did he tell you I keep them?
There's a... a box in there,
but it's too high up for me.
Cole's always the one who does it.
Hello?
Yes, this is she.
What do you mean, some kind of accident?
Oh.
They say he was in his cell
when it happened.
My... my baby. My baby...
Oh, God, my baby!
Oh, my babies!
All my... All my babies is gone!
All my babies is gone!
Where's the Fist?
- Name, please.
- Daniel Rand, of Rand Enterprises.
- Here to see?
- The CEOs of Midland Circle Financial.
- Are they expecting you?
- Not like this.
Right this way.
My name is Danny Rand.
Last year, you illegally transferred
$243 million worth of assets
through my family's company.
And you thought you got away with it.
But I know who you are.
You killed my parents, attacked my home.
You're the Hand.
And I'm gonna make sure...
Mr. Rand.
I appreciate your candor.
And your passion.
And I must say,
considering what I've heard about you,
you seem much more disciplined
than I anticipated.
- And who are you?
- I'm in charge.
But, please, go on.
You were telling us
what you were going to do.
- Murdock!
- We need to leave now.
If you grab me like that again,
I'll punch you so hard, you'll see.
- I've been here before.
- Why are following me?
- And you're in serious danger.
- What kind of lawyer are you?
This case you took, it's leading you
toward something truly sinister.
Okay, you are the most full of shit lawyer
I've ever met,
and I think we should appreciate
the magnitude of that statement.
- Let's talk about this somewhere else.
- Let's talk about it never.
Unless you wanna tell me
how a blind man moves the way you do.
- Excuse me?
- I have pictures, asshole.
Rand Enterprises has put together
a case to take you down.
Extortion, narcotics, human trafficking...
There's no end to what we'll uncover.
And?
And you can't hide anymore.
- Does it look like we're hiding?
- Behind Midland Circle Financial.
Behind corporate shells,
or street-level criminals who don't know
who they're working for. Yes.
It's what you do.
But I'm here to expose you.
I am the Immortal Iron Fist,
weapon of K'un-Lun.
- And I'm fulfilling my destiny.
- K'un-Lun.
How is it these days?
You're gonna lose everything.
Just like I did.
You haven't lost everything, Mr. Rand.
Not yet.
- What are you doing?
- Gunshot.
- Where?
- In the penthouse.
- How do you know that?
- I just do.
This is exactly what I was trying
to avoid. I need that.
I've crossed paths with Iron Fists before,
but this is different,
because this time...
I won't kill you.
No use using her for protection.
They will rip right through her
to get to you.
Come on!
- You?
- Me.
So punching's okay now?
It's complicated.
You look like an asshole.
It's your scarf.
- Jessica?
- Luke.
- How you been?
- Long story.
We have to get out of here.
- Who's he?
- Longer story. Who's he?
Wait. There's someone else coming.
Something else.
You know what to do.
- What is it?
- Oh, shit.
- Who's that?
- Bad news. We gotta go.
Uh-oh!
Ah!
Elektra?
Come on.
Who are you people?